A Guide to the WAGE Radio Collection, 1958-2003
Thomas Balch Library
- (AV 006)
  - Recordings (titles taken directly from reel-to-reel tape boxes)
    - Vol. 51, 5/15 to 5/21, 21 May 1982
    - Vol. 52, 5/21 to 6/2/82, 2 June 1982
    - Vol. 53, 6/3/82 to 6/9/82, 9 June 1982
    - Vol. 54, 6/12 to 6/22/82, 22 June 1982
    - Vol. 55, 6/23 to 7/2, 2 July 1982
    - Vol. 56, 7/3/82 to 7/17/82, 17 July 1982
    - Vol. 57, 7/17 to 7/27/82, 27 July 1982
    - Vol. 58, 7/27 to 8/7/82, 7 August 1982
    - Vol. 59, 8/10 to 8/26/82, 26 August 1982
    - Vol. 60, 8/27 to 9/15, 15 September 1982
    - Master Tape Vol. 61, 9/18-9/27 '82, 27 September 1982
    - Vol. 62, 9/27 to 10/7/82, 7 October 1982
    - Vol. 63, 10/7 to 10/15, 15 October 1982
    - Vol. 64 pt. 1, 10/15 to 10/25, 25 October 1982
    - Vol. 64 pt. 2 ,10/27 to 11/5/82, 5 November 1982
    - Vol. 33, n.d.
    - Vol. 33, n.d. n.d.
  - Recordings (titles taken directly from reel-to-reel tape boxes)
    - Vol. 65, 11/5/82 to 11/17/82, 17 November 1982
    - Vol. 66, 11/17 to 11/30/82, 30 November 1982
    - Vol. 67, 11/30/82 to 12/15, 15 December 1982
    - CARTS Vol. 68, 12/15 to 12/28/82, 28 December 1982
    - Vol. 69, 12/28 to 1/7/83, 7 January 1983
    - Vol. 70, 1/10/83 to 1/18/83, 18 January 1983
    - Vol. 71, 1/18/83 to 1/28/83, 28 January 1983
    - Vol. 72, 1/29 to 2/8/83, 8 February 1983
    - CARTS 2/8 to 2/16/83 Vol. 73, 16 February 1983
    - Vol. 74, Feb 16 to 24 1983, 24 February 1983
    - Vol. 75, Feb. 25th to 3/7/83, 7 March 1983
    - Vol. 76, 3/7/83 to 3/15/83, 15 March 1983
    - Vol. 77, 3/15 to 3/26/83, 26 March 1983
    - Vol. 78, 3/25/83 to 4/1/83, 1 April 1983
    - Vol. 79, 4-1 to 4-13-83, 13 April 1983
    - CARTS Vol. 80, 4/13 to 4/21/83, 21 April 1983
    - Vol. 81, Apr. 21 to Apr. 27, 27 April 1983
    - Vol. 82, 4/28 to 5/5/83, 5 May 1983
    - Vol. 83, 5/5/83 to 5/13/83, 13 May 1983
    - CARTS Vol. 84, 5/13 to 5/20/83, 20 May 1983
    - Vol. 85, 5/20 to 5/27/83, 27 May 1983
    - Vol. 86, 5/26 to 6/6/83, 6 June 1983
    - Vol. 87, 6/7 to 6/14, 14 June 1983
    - CARTS Vol. 88, 6/15 to 6/22/83, 22 June 1983
    - Vol. 89, 6/22 to 7/2/83, 2 July 1983
    - Vol. 90, 7/2 to 7/12/83, 12 July 1983
    - Vol. 91, 7/13 to 7/21/83, 21 July 1983
    - Vol. 92, 7/22/83, 22 July 1983
    - Vol. 93, 7/29 to 8/9/83, 9 August 1983
    - Vol. 94, 8/10 to 8/18, 18 August 1983
    - Vol. 94b, 8/11 and 12 8/18 to 8/26, 23 August 1983
    - Vol. 95, 8/28 to 9/2/83, 2 September 1983
    - CARTS Vol. 96, 9/3 to 9/9/83, 9 September 1983
    - Vol. 97, 9/10 to 9/17/83, 17 September 1983
  - Recordings (titles taken directly from reel-to-reel tape boxes)
    - Rouge Dragon 1968, 14 March 1968
    - 11-30-71 Leesburg By Pass, 30 November 1971
    - UK Trip Vol. 1, 1972, 1 January 1972
    - UK Trip Vol. 2, 1972, 1 January 1972
    - Vets Day 1972, Senator Scott, 23 October 1972
    - WAGE News 1972 General Elections, 1 November 1972
    - Drug Use 1973, 1 January 1973
    - Bits and Pieces of Broadway 1 1974, 1 January 1974
    - Claire and her School Board Show (news special), 19 January 1974
    - Memorial Day 1974 Rollins Hill Murry, 1 May 1974
    - Commonwealth Bank Dedication July 1974 (Saturday the 27th), 27 July 1974
    - Vietnam and Cambodia 1975, 1 January 1975
    - Waddell, Rollins, Murphy news conference, 27 February 1975
    - NVCC Opening 3/75 [tape 1], 1 March 1975
    - NVCC Opening 3/75 [tape 2], 1 March 1975
    - S-Citizens Show 1975, 11 May 1975
    - Quiz Show 1975, 1 June 1975
    - Democratic HQ, 10 June 1975
    - PNB opening, 12 July 1975
    - Apollo-Soyuz 1, 17 July 1975
    - Apollo-Soyuz 2, 17 July 1975
    - Governor Godwin Speech to General Assembly 1-76, 14 January 1976
    - Dowty Rotol Dedication Ceremonies, 19 October 1976
    - The Swearing In of Jimmy Carter, 20 January 1977
    - Humphrey Memorial Service, 15 January 1978
    - Ad-Hoc Reassessments Committee, 26 November 1978
    - #2 VAB, n.d.
    - #3 VAB 0000-1446 SBE, n.d.
    - At Large Chairman debate, van Huyck/Hyatt, 8/14 demo forum, n.d.
    - News Special Blue Ridge Democrat Forum 8/13, n.d.
    - VAB 4, n.d.
  - Recordings (titles taken directly from reel-to-reel tape boxes)
    - Memorial Day 1967, Wilbur Hall Died, 21 August 1972
    - News Conference 1974, 1 January 1974
    - Godwin Inaugural, 12 January 1974
    - Hospital Dedication, 27 June 1974
    - Veterans Day 1974 General News 1 of 2, 11 November 1974
    - Memorial Day 1975, 30 May 1975
    - Vol. 1 Newsbeat Jun-July 1975, 31 July 1975
    - 11-8-75 to 12-27-75 Vol. 6 Weekend Report, 27 December 1975
    - Compass Year End 1975, 31 December 1975
    - Year End 1975 Fall of Indochina, 31 December 1975
    - Gerald Ford 1976, 1 January 1976
    - From Live News Conference, 29 March 1976
    - Vol. 2 Compass 1976, 15 May 1976
    - July 4th 1976 Leesburg, 4 July 1976
    - Year End Compass Report Tape Vol. 3, 5-77-76 to 7-17-76, 17 July 1976
    - Year End Compass Tape Vol. 4 1976, 7-17 to 9-25-76, 25 September 1976
    - Vets Day Speaker 1976 (LCHS), 11 November 1976
    - Year End Compass Report 1976 Vol. 5, 31 December 1976
    - Year End Compass, 11-20-76 to 1-1-77, 1 January 1976
    - Year End Compass 1976, 1 January 1977
    - Compass Year End Vol. 2 1977, 25 March 1977
    - Compass Year End Vol. 3 1977, 3-26 to 4-23, 23 April 1977
    - Compass Master Tape Vol. 4 1977, 24 April 1977
    - Compass Report Vol. 6 1977, 29 September 1977
    - Vol. 7 Compass Master, 8-26 to 9-30 '77, 30 September 1977
    - Compass Master Tape Vol. 8, Sept. 30th to Oct. 29th, 1977, 29 October 1977
    - 1977 Compass Vol. 1, 31 December 1977
    - Compass Vol. 5 1977, 31 December 1977
    - Compass Master Tape Vol. 9, 11/5/77 thru 1/21/78, 21 January 1978
    - Compass Master Tape Vol. 10, 1/28/78 to 2/18/78, 18 February 1978
    - Compass Reports Vol. 1, 1976 to 3-6-76, 6 June 1978
    - Dialogue: Radical Woman Educator, 6 June 1979
    - Know Your County, n.d.
  - Recordings (titles taken directly from reel-to-reel tape boxes)
    - FAA Dedication (2), 15 June 1963
    - Goose Creek, 6 January 1967
    - Hijack, 5 May 1967
    - Oatlands Conference, 8 May 1972
    - 1972 Memorial Day Services, 30 May 1972
    - Veterans Day 1974 2 of 2 General News, 11 November 1972
    - 1972 General Election, 30 November 1972
    - Watergate O'Brien Larry (Democratic Official), 21 May 1972
    - Memorial Day Services 1973 Dewey Mill and Other Officials, 30 May 1973
    - Veterans Day 1973 Harry Byrd, 11 November 1973
    - Watergate 1973, 31 December 1973
    - Oatlands Vol. 1 1974, 31 December 1974
    - Oatlands Vol. 2 1974, 31 December 1974
    - Story of 1974--Nixon, 31 December 1974
    - Sue Snaman Master Tape 1974 Vol. 1, 31 December 1974
    - Captain Jack, 17 June 1975
    - County Office Ground Breaking [1], 16 September 1975
    - County Office Ground Breaking [2], 16 September 1975
    - Vol. 5 Weekend, 8/29/75 to 11/2/75, 2 November 1975
    - Veteran's Day 1975, 11 November 1975
    - Grand Opening Tennis Court - Leesburg, St. Park Auto (remote), 31 December 1975
    - News Conference, 27 March 1976
    - Special Olympics w/B. Brundage, 11 May 1976
    - Valley Football R1, 20 November 1976
    - Valley-Orange Football reel 2, 20 November 1976
    - LV - Southampton FOS 2nd Half, 27 November 1976
    - Know Your County (used also as a "Compass"), 23 April 1977
    - Memorial Day, 30 May 1977
    - Runaway Series 1979, 31 December 1977
    - 0-33 Energy Program - ???/Elem P. Bolen, 20 June 1979
    - UDI Top 10 1979, 31 December 1979
    - Mt. Zion Church 116th Anniversary, 16 April 1983
    - Sterling Park Anniversary, 11 September 1983
    - 1986 Loudoun Magazine File Tape #1, 31 December 1986
    - WAGE "In Focus on Ashburn" 1/30/87 Steve Porter, 30 January 1987
  - Recordings (titles taken directly from reel-to-reel tape boxes)
    - Blizzard 66, 13 February 1966
    - 10th Anniversary WAGE 1968, 1 January 1968
    - Orrison - Final Newsbeat, 24 July 1970
    - Highway 1971, 30 October 1971
    - Land Use 1972, 1 January 1972
    - Route 7 Hearing 1973, 1 January 1973
    - S.S.T. 1973, 1 January 1973
    - Supervisors 1973, 1 January 1973
    - Drug Report, 14 May 1973
    - Flood 1 year later 1973, 22 June 1973
    - J.F. Kennedy 12-31-63, 22 November 1973
    - B. of S. Planning Session 1974, 1 January 1974
    - B. of S. Planning Session, 1 October 1974
    - EBS Closed Circuit Test, 21 February 1975
    - McDonald C.K., 27 June 1975
    - Earl Bell at Memorial Day Services 1976, 31 May 1976
    - BOS: Court Bond Issue Proposal 1 hour, 1 January 1977
    - Budget PM #1, 9 May 1977
    - Public Hearing Budget 1977-78 Vol. 2 5-9-77, 9 May 1977
    - Public Hearing Budget 77-78 PM session, 9 May 1977
    - Water Hearing #1, 21 November 1977
    - Water Hearing #2, 21 November 1977
    - Year in Review 1977 WAGE News, 1 January 1978
    - Budget Hearing - LC BOS 3:00 P, 30 May 1978
    - Budget Hearing - LC BOS 4:00 P, 30 May 1978
    - Budget Hearing - LC BOS 7:00 P, 30 May 1978
    - Budget Hearing - LC BOS 8:00 P, 30 May 1978
    - Police Office 1978 Roy Smith Award, 19 December 1978
    - Know Your County - Loudoun Memorial, 11 November 1979
    - WAGE Magazine Tape/VAB LOG CB 1990, 1 January 1990
    - Actuality Tape, 1 February 1990
    - Mike's Campaign Tape, 1 May 1990
    - NVCC Today Show "Recycle for life", 4 October 1992
    - December 1993 Archives, 1 December 1993
    - Carter Trial - voicers & soundbites, n.d.
    - Republican Forum 8/22 (News Special) Run 19:28, n.d.
    - VAB 5, n.d.
    - VAB 6, n.d.
    - WAGE Magazine tape 3/15, n.d.
    - Year in Review, n.d.
    - Carlton Penn 1977, 1 January 1977
  - Recordings (titles taken directly from reel-to-reel tape boxes)
    - Blue Ridge Middle School 1972, 1 January 1972
    - Easter Paxton Home 72, 1 January 1972
    - England 1972, 1 January 1972
    - Flood 1972 [1], 1 January 1972
    - Flood 1972 [2], 1 January 1972
    - Transpo '72, 1 January 1972
    - Hickory Hill 1972, 1 January 1972
    - Holton-Waddell-Blimp 1972, 1 January 1972
    - Interviews in England 1972 while on US Planning Workshop, 1 January 1972
    - Sessions at Planning Workshop in England 1972, 1 January 1972
    - Transpo '72-HELA, 1 January 1972
    - Transpo '72 PSA's, 1 January 1972
    - Waterford Water-Sewer 1972, 1 January 1972
    - Waterford Water-Sewer 72, 1 January 1972
    - Apollo 16, 16 April 1972
    - Apollo 16, 16 April 1972
    - LB and G Fire, 24 May 1972
    - Xerox, 28 August 1972
    - Lucketts Dedication, 24 October 1972
    - "A Landslide for a President" WAGE News UPI/72, 1 November
    - 1972 Political Cuts, 1 November 1972
    - Election 1972, 1 November 1972
    - White House 1972, 1 November 1972
    - LARC School opening 1972, 12 November 1972
    - 1977 VAB New Entry Master, 31 December 1972
    - Deere - Waterloo 1973, 1 January 1973
    - England - Planning 1973, 1 January 1973
    - England #2 1973, 1 January 1973
    - Rollins-Waddell 1973, 1 January 1973
    - Wadell Sings 1973, 1 January 1973
    - Sky Lab 5/73, 1 May 1973
    - Watergate, 7 May 1973
    - Clorox 1973, 1 June 1973
    - SST 9/29/73 & 9/30/73, 23 September 1973
    - Highway Design Hearing, 25 September 1973
    - Reply to "Tatum" by Nutter 1973 PCD, 3 October 1973
    - Dallas 1973, 22 November 1973
    - JFK, 22 November 1973
    - J.B.Vorous, 1 January 1974
    - Watergate, 1 January 1974
    - North American Bank, 15 April 1974
    - "Compass" SST Report Weekend Round Table, 1 January 1975
    - 1975 UPI News Logo, 1 January 1975
    - Farm Tour 1977 Garcia, 1 January 1975
    - Johnson, 1 January 1975
    - New Opp. 1975, 1 January 1975
    - Drug Bust - Lee. Florist, 13 June 1975
    - SB 208 1975, 27 June 1975
    - Contract Signing County Office Building, 21 August 1975
    - VAB 1976 SST, 1 January 1976
    - Panama Canal 1977, 1 January 1977
    - Fire in Purcellville Frank Lambert, 11 February 1977
    - Helping Hand Fire - Special Report, 13 October 1978
    - VA UPI Awards 1979, 4 May 1979
  - VHS Tapes and Cassettes
    - WAGE on CNN (VHS), 13 March 1995
    - WAGE Bridal "An Affair of the Heart" (VHS), n.d.
    - Bill and PCD's Closing Comments on 1290 (cassette), n.d.
- (OMB 017)
    - 10th Anniversary Correspondence, 1968
    - Advertisements, 1982-1987
    - Event Posters, 1986-1992
    - Newspaper Articles, 1958-2003
    - 16 x 20 inch framed WAGE collage (VC 0053), 1996
- (VC 0053)
  - Photographs (1977-1998)
  - Photographs (n.d.)